---
Define: Fader Jockey
Answer: Fader Jockey is a name given to audio mixers
---
Define: Foldback
Answer: Foldback is audio that is fed back onto the stage for the performers
---
Define: Musical Theater Sound
---
Define: Theater Sound
Answer: All aural elements of a show, including the sound of the space, sound system, and practical noises, whether intentional or unintentional during a show.
---
Define: Theatrical Mixer
Answer: A sound mixer that is especially trained to mix theater line by line and in the requirements of mixing for theater.
---
Question: What is the difference between a sitzprobe and a wandleprobe?
Answer: In a sitzprobe the performers are usually seated and not allowed much movement in the acting area.  A wandleprobe they are allowed and encouraged, if not required, to perform in the space and wander the stage while performing to learn the space.
---
Question: "2/3 of a mixer's job is communication: Tell someone to shut up and have them walk away smiling.  What are some examples that Shannon gives of exactly this?"
Answer: 
---
Question: "What are some of the goals of a sitzprobe or wandleprobe?"
Answer: 
---
Question: "If a mixer and a designer disagree on what sounds good, who wins?"
Answer: "The a designer tells you as a mixer to mix something a certain way, you mix it as the designer wants.  As a mixer your job is to execute the designer's vision."
---
Define: Foley
---
Define: Sound Designer
---
Define: Sound Operator
---
Question: "Name at least two of the major sound shops in NYC"
Answer: "Masque Sound, PRG, Sound Associates"
---
Question: "What was the first sound recording known to have been used in theater?"
Answer: "Shannon cites an often repeated sound of Vladamir Lenin's voice in Rasputin, however Wikipedia cites a baby crying in 1890, well before this.  Either answer is acceptable"
---
Question: "Who was the first person known to be given the title of sound designer in theater?"
Answer: "David Collison at London's Lyric Theater, Hammersmith in 1959"
---
Question: "Who was the first person known to be given the title sound designer in regional theater?"
Answer:
---
Question: "Who is considered to be the godfather of theater sound?  What made him different from other sound designers at the time."
Answer: "Abe Jacob is considered to be the godfather of modern theater sound design, and he was different because he came from the world of rock and roll concerts, and brought this knowledge to theater to transform how musicals were performed and designed"
---
Define: A1
Answer: Heads up the sound run crew for a show, mixes the FoH for the show
---
Define: A2
Answer: Can vary, generally called a deck sound, they are responsible for the sound of the show from the plaster line back, including monitors, mics, etc.  They can also be responsible for the monitor mix
---
Define: Conceptual Sound Design
---
Define: Monitor Mixer
---
Question: "Describe the differences commonly found between straight play sound design and musical theater sound design, as described by Shannon Slaton?"
Answer:
---
Question: "Complete the following: Being a designer is not about knowing the answer, but..."
Answer: Being a designer is not about knowing the answer, but knowing how to get it and how to explain it so everyone understands
---
Question:  What must a sound designer do if he wants to be considered successful?
Answer: He must make everyone who works for him successful.  A failure on the designer's team reflects directly on the designer.
---
Question: "What is the difference between a assistant designer and an associate designer?"
Answer: "An associate designer has the ability to speak for the designer and make design decisions in his absence, an assistant designer has no ability to make design decisions and acts primarily as an information funnel to the designer along with maintaining paperwork."
---
Define: Area Mic'ing
---
Define: Blackbox Theater